好了 搞定五个牛顿方程
Okay, five Newtonian equations down.
只剩七个量子力学证明了
Only seven quantum mechanical proofs to go!
小宇宙被甲烷点燃
We are cooking with C-H-4.
用燃气点燃
Cooking with gas.
她俩都单身 兄弟们
And they're both single, fellas.
拜托 各位 我们就不能
Come on, guys. Can't we just have one day
互相尊重 互相支持一下吗
where we respect and support one another?
大家好啊 我的家人们
Hello, family.
我们的年度街区派对
There was an incident this morning
在今天早上出了点意外
at our annual neighborhood block party.
通常都是小卡负责娱乐活动
Cam usually provides the entertainment at these things,
但他今天有莉莉的生日派对 所以菲尔自愿帮忙
but he had Lily's birthday party, so Phil volunteered.
有了菲尔宝 谁要菲茨宝
Who needs a Fizbo if you can have a Philbo?
什么
What?!
什么时候才能停啊
I mean, where does it end?
好长啊 仔细想想
It's so long! It's comically long,
长得好好笑啊
when you think about it.
问题是 菲尔很怕小丑
Thing is, Phil's terrified of clowns.
我以为如果我自己是小丑 应该不会害怕
Just thought if I was the clown, I wouldn't be scared.
就好比给自己挠痒痒就不痒了一样
Like how you can't tickle yourself.
塞巴斯蒂安 别跑
Sebastian, no!
我来搞定 塞巴斯蒂安
I got this! Sebastian!
你妈在担心你呀 伙计
Your mom's worried about you, buddy,
虽然完全没必要...
even though there's absolutely no reason to be --
闻起来... 天呐
Smell -- oh, God.
像...
S-s-
小丑...
s-clowns!
亲爱的
Honey.
到处都是小丑
They were everywhere.
我意识到我今天早上给我们家丢脸了
I recognize that I embarrassed the family this morning,
但我跟你们保证
but I assure you that --
菲尔 亲爱的 过来一下
Phil, honey, just come on over here for one second.
稍等片刻
Just a sec.
亲爱的 你不是第一个穿上小丑服
Honey, you are not the first person to put on a clown outfit,
走进满是镜子的房间 然后...
walk into a hall of mirrors, and --
我的意思是说
I guess what I'm saying
如果你觉得你有必要做点什么
is if you think you need to do something
来弥补早上的事情
to make up for that,
别这么想
don't think that.
不
No!
天哪 死机了
Oh, my God, the computer froze!
老爸来救你
Daddy to the rescue!
我觉得他听到了
Well, I feel heard.
好吧 老爸 我觉得没关系
Yeah, you know what, Dad, I-I think it's okay.
我只需要强制重置
I just need to do a hard reset --
不 我觉得这不是重置的问题
No, I don't think it's a reset issue.
我觉得是突波保护器坏了
I think the surge protector just blew.
我要直接给这玩意儿
I am going to plug this bad boy directly
插上电源...
into the wall and..
天哪 你烧了我的电脑
Oh, my God! You fried my computer!
我们的作业都没了
All of our work is gone!
亲爱的 冷静 这些硬盘都经过设计
Honey, calm down. These hard drives are designed
可以承受高温...
to withstand temperatures of up --
天哪 着火了
Oh, my God, it's on fire!
该死
Damn it.
怎么了
What is wrong?
没事
Huh? Nothing.
我完全忘了我的海军兄弟们
You know, I totally forgot some of my Navy buddies
一会儿要在市中心的
are meeting downtown later
欧布莱恩酒吧小聚
for a little reunion at O'Brien's pub.
今天没什么特别的事情
Well, nothing special is happening here today,
我允许你去
so you have permission to go.
我本来也不需要你的允许啊
Well, I don't really need your permission.
你为什么不闭嘴 免得我改变主意
Why don't you just keep quiet and take yes for an answer?
我的帅气 厉害 完美的儿子来了
Ay, there's my handsome, perfect, amazing boy!
我不会去班级旅行的
Still not going on the class trip.
你为什么这么傻 是因为我...
Why are you being such a dummy? Is this because I --
老妈 我不想聊这个
Mom, I don't want to talk about it.
为什么这家里只有我一个人
Why am I the only one in this house
愿意聊事情呢
that ever wants to talk about things?!
宝贝 怎么啦
Ay, papi, what is wrong?
不是时候
Not now.
好了 够了
Okay, that's it.
如果这家里的爷们都不跟我说话
If the men in this house don't start talking to me,
我向天发誓 我会让你们每个人
I swear to God that I will make life miserable
都没有好日子过
for each and every one of you!
不 等一下
No, not yet.
别告诉我停电了
Oh, don't tell me the power just went out!
我的智能床垫要停在小睡模式了
My Sleep Number bed is stuck on the nap setting.
冷静
Calm down.
这就是为什么我要买新的发电机
This is exactly why I sprung for a new generator.
刚刚开了 不用谢
which, you're welcome, just kicked in.
当然了 没办法给所有电器供电
Now, granted, it doesn't power everything.
所以我得作出一些艰难的抉择
I had to make some hard choices.
所以只通酒吧和台球桌吗
That's it? The bar and the pool table?
冰箱都是黑的
The frigerator's black.
好了 杰 在给重要的几样电器
Okay, Jay, you're not leaving
通完电之前 你不准走
until you put power in the important things.
我向天发誓 别把我逼得更生气
I swear to God, don't make me more mad than I already am!
就不能等我回来再弄吗
Can't I just do it when I get back?
电母您能消停一会儿不
Would you stop doing that?!
今天是莉莉的八岁生日
It's Lily's 8th birthday,
我们本打算在后院办个小型派对
and we had a little backyard party planned.
准备些热狗 气球
Hot dogs, some balloons --
我们就打算随便弄一下
you know, I mean, we really just threw it together.
就好像我去年的生日派对
Kind of like my birthday party last year.
好了 是你告诉我你不想要我做什么...
Okay, you told me that you did not want me to do anything --
总之我们本来打算办一个简单的儿童派对
Anyway, we were all set for a casual kids' party,
但是莉莉收到了一封邮件
but then Lily got an e-mail.
她要来 她要来 她要来 阿什利要来
She's coming! She's coming! She's coming! Ashley's coming!
阿什利要来吗
Ashley's coming?
米奇尔 阿什利要来
Mitchell, Ashley's coming!
天哪 等一下
Oh, my God! Well, now, wait a minute.
阿什利·S还是阿什利·W
Ashley S. Or Ashley W.?
W
"W"!
阿什利·W要来
Ashley W.'s coming!
阿什利是莉莉班上最受欢迎的女孩
Ashley is the most popular girl in Lily's class.
就是说 你请是请了她
I mean, you invite her...
但你觉得她是永远不可能来的
but you never think she's gonna accept.
不 一定是哪里出错了 或者...
No. Something must have fallen through, or --
重点是她能决定以后谁能和大家一起玩
The point is, she decides who's in and who's out.
所以我们得提高派对的档次
So we had to up our game.
这是个非常有趣的挑战
Which was a fun challenge.
是啊 考虑到我们已经有一段时间
Yeah, considering it had been a while
没有办什么很华丽的生日派对了
since we'd thrown any sort of fabulous birthday party.
你求我别搞得太大的 你说...
You begged me not to make a fuss. You said --
因为我就是那种人对吧
Oh, because that sounds like me, yeah.
好了 等索菲上车
All right. Once Sophie boards the bus,
我们就去公主公园
we will be on our way to the Princess Park,
每个人可以选她的公主服
where we will all pick out our princess costumes!
我觉得阿什利玩得挺开心的
I think Ashley's having a really good time.
是吗 你怎么知道
Yeah? How can you tell?
她人还没走
She's still here.
不 这是下雨了吗
Oh, no! Is it raining?
别担心 亲爱的 我们有遮阳伞
Not to worry, sweetie. We have parasols.
可以了
It worked!
好了 我把几个重要电器都通上电了
Good. I powered up all your essentials.
我要去见我的兄弟们了
Now I'm gonna go meet my buddies.
看来我的意式咖啡机不算重要电器
I see my espresso machine didn't make the cut,
但我忍一忍吧
but I'll manage.
我要见的兄弟里有一个曾经在大海上迷失方向
One of the guys I'm meeting was lost at sea once.
他不得不吃水母为生
Had to eat a jellyfish.
我会向他夸你很勇敢的
I'll speak to him of your courage.
没电了 不得不过来 快速讲两句
So, power's out. Had to come over. Real quick.
菲尔打扮成小丑
Phil got dressed up as a clown
走进一间全是镜子的房间恐慌发作
and then had a panic attack in a hall of mirrors,
所以他想补偿一下
so he's gonna be looking to overcompensate for a lot,
所以请别太沉浸于....
so please don't indulge in any of his --
-杰 -来了
- Hey, Jay. - Right here.
我记得你有台发电机
I remembered you had a generator.
我要给艾丽克斯上传几个文件
I'm just gonna upload a few quick files for Alex.
-别问了 -我从来没问过
- Don't ask. - I never do.
我打不开这瓶子
I can't open the jar.
幸运的你有个好叔叔
Well, lucky for you your uncle --
好姐夫菲尔在此
brother-in-law Phil is here.
只需要轻轻一拧
And with one mighty twi--
我们应该就能
We should be...
打开它了
good to go.
-不 -不 不 不
-No! -No, no, no, no, no!
不 不
No, no, no!
爸 别再帮倒忙了
Dad, stop helping!
你好啊 小怪兽
Hey, monster.
你好啊
Hey, you.
安迪和我的关系有一个火热激情的开端
Andy and I started out pretty hot and heavy,
不过这两周我特别得忙
but, uh, the last few weeks I've just been super busy,
所以我猜他感觉自己被忽略了
so I guess he's feeling neglected,
所以他反应也有点冷淡
and he's acting a little cold.
就在胳膊上拍两下算什么
I mean, a chuck on the arm?
我们是哈克·费恩和汤姆·索亚的关系吗
What are we, Huck Finn and Tom Sawyer?
是有这么两个人 对吧
Those are people, right?
这里有一滩水
Ay, there's a puddle!
史黛拉或者乔弄的
Stella or Joe.
过几个小时见
I'll see you in a couple of hours.
不 不 不 看 漏水了
No, no, no, no! Look, it's a leak,
因为是从墙缝留下来的
because it's coming through the wall.
应该是房顶的排水槽又堵了
Most likely your gutters backed up.
包在我身上了
Consider it handled.
跪求别叫我 跪求别叫我
Please don't ask me. Please don't ask me.
卢克 修排水槽去
Luke! To the gutters!
小公主们 城堡到了
Okay, princesses, your castle awaits!
怎么回事
What gives?
路上开始漫水了
The roads were starting to flood,
所以我们想来这里躲风暴
so we were hoping to ride out the storm here.
当然
Yeah, sure.
还有 爸 我们想继续公主的主题
Also, Dad, we're hoping to keep the princess theme alive,
所以如果你可以假装
so if you could pretend to be a --
-感兴趣吗 -不
- Interested? - No.
好吧
Okay.
女士们 到变装时间了 我们有...
Ladies, it's costume time! We have...
公主装
Costumes!
贝儿 埃尔莎和爱丽儿
Belle, we have Elsa, we have Ariel!
公主装
Costumes?
额 公主装
Ew, costumes.
当我们几岁 五岁吗
What are we, 5?
好吧
Okay.
好吧 真的发生了
Uh, okay, so, that's happening.
阿什利讨厌公主装
Hey, Ashley hates the costumes.
你们得想点别的招儿
You got to think of something else!
-我们要做什么 -我不知道
- What do we do? - Well, I don't know.
我们的小伙伴们是一帮八岁的女孩
Our friends are basically 8-year-old girls.
她们会想干什么
What would they want to do?
舞蹈派对
Dance party!
好吗 好吧 女孩们
Yeah? Yeah? Okay. Okay, girls.
我们来放点音乐吧
Uh, let's get some music started here, huh?
天哪 小卡 没电
Oh, God, Cam, there's no power.
有"卡"电
There's Cam power.
那是啥
What is that?
我要是听了你的没给国家公共广播频道捐款
Well, had I listened to you and we not donated to NPR,
我们就不会拿到这台免费的应急收音机
we wouldn't have gotten this free emergency radio
并转送给杰和歌洛莉亚
that we then re-gifted to Jay and Gloria.
每个月19刀不算免费吧 不过随便你
I wouldn't call $19 a month free, but okay.
好了 女士们 让我们浪起来
All right, let's get a little funk in here, ladies!
好吧
Okay.
再加点浪能量进去
Little more funky energy in this thing!
这东西需要先热身
Got to warm up, you know?
得让它热起来
Got to get it warmed up!
我到底是怎么了
I don't know what's wrong with me.
我这只手可是专拌黄油的
This is my butter-churning arm.
左边第三个抽屉里
Third drawer from the left.
我不懂你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
谢谢 你怎么还穿着睡袍啊
Thank you. What's with the robe?
我得出去把我的抗旱花园盖住
I had to go outside and cover my drought-resistant garden.
这雨来得可真是时候
Timing, right?
反正 我的房间没有电
Well, anyway, there's no power in my room,
我不想摸着黑穿衣服 所以
and I wasn't gonna get dressed in the dark, so...
你爸挺疯狂的吧
How crazy is your dad, huh?!
勇敢面对大自然的挑战
Braving the elements!
为了全家不湿身 真是贴心小棉袄
Keeping the family dry! That is fur!
你要干嘛 卢克
What's the plan, Luke?
有想法是好的
There are no bad ideas,
可是在电闪雷鸣的风暴里挥着金属铲
but waving a metal shovel around in an electrical storm
有点不太好吧
could have a downside,
我们还是把它放回车库吧
so let's put it back in the garage, huh?
真的好险
Whoa, that was close!
天哪 不会又来了吧
Oh, my God! Not again!
宝贝 你会没事的
Oh, honey, you're gonna be fine.
你竟然又让他被雷劈了
I can't believe you let him get struck again!
又
Again?
别担心 小傻瓜
Don't worry about it, champ.
雷应该没劈到他
I don't even think it hit him.
上次他闻着有铝的味儿
Last time he smelled like aluminum.
上次
Last time?!
宝贝 你爸和我在说话呢
Honey, your father and I are trying to talk.
好了 各位
Okay, everyone.
你们不用等我
Don't feel like you have to wait for me to get back.
杰
Jay!
漏水变严重了
The leak is growing!
我正要再去修呢
I was just on my way back out.
-我来吧 -可是
- I'll do it. - But --
坐下
Sit!
这种逃避学校出游的办法太傻了
That's a silly excuse not to go to your school trip.
妈 我想好了
Mom, I've made my decision.
发生什么事了
What's going on here?
气氛紧张得我都能拿弯刀劈开了
I could cut the tension with my machete.
其实 不算什么事
It's so... nothing.
曼尼的睡袍
I mean Manny got his robe
被冰箱门夹住了
caught in the refrigerator door,
所以我不小心看到了
and I may have accidentally seen...
他的身子
him.
你看到了
Oh, you saw.
好了 曼尼 都结束了
Okay. Manny, it's over.
已经发生的就发生了
What happened happened.
都结束了
It's done.
好吧 我有个事情
Okay, good, because I have a problem
需要你帮忙 克莱尔
and I need your help, Claire.
没问题 什么事
Yes. You got it. What is it?
曼尼不想去学校的旅行
Well, Manny doesn't want to go to his school trip
因为有传言
because there is a rumor
这帮孩子们要去裸泳
that the kids want to go skinny-dipping,
所以他对自己的身材很没信心
and he's self-conscious about his body.
我得装作不理解为什么
I'm gonna pretend I don't understand
你要把我拖进这场对话
why you're including me in this conversation.
我只是想说
I'm just saying --
你就告诉他吧 反正你都偷看过了
You could tell him since you already peeped.
我没偷看
I didn't peep.
告诉他他身材很好
Tell him that he has a beautiful body
这样你的偷看还是有点正面作用的
so at least something good comes out of the peeping.
请不要再说了
Please stop saying that.
等我看到卢克的裸体 我会告诉他
When I see Luke naked, I am going to tell him,
"卢克 你的身材很好"
"Luke, you have a beautiful body".
什么时候
"When"?
也许她不觉得我身材好
Maybe she doesn't think I have a beautiful body.
不是吧 克莱尔 是真的吗
iAy, dios mio! Claire, is this true?
不 我做不到
No! Okay, I can't do this.
我现在就走开
I'm -- I'm just gonna go ahead and walk away now.
不过如果万一有雷要劈这栋房子
But if a bolt of lightning should strike this house,
你可以让它找我
you can send it my way.
什么 她们不喜欢花生酱三明治
What -- they didn't like the peanut-butter sandwiches?
不 阿什利开了口之后就没有人去碰了
No. No one would touch them after Ashley said,
"这也配叫松脆"
"Crunchy?"
你没事吧 她就在那呢
What are you, crazy? She's right there.
真可笑
This is ridiculous.
我们真的能让一个八岁孩子掌控派对节奏吗
Are we really gonna let an 8-year-old dictate this party?
你也知道同龄压力有多大
You know how peer pressure is.
我像莉莉那么大 也遇到过阿什利那样的人
I had an Ashley when I was Lily's age.
她不让我在食堂和她坐一桌
She blackballed me from the cafeteria table,
之后就没人愿意跟我同桌了
and then no one would sit with me.
我只能在外面和班里的公鸡一块吃饭
I had to eat outside with the class rooster.
然后有一天...
And then one day...
好 如果结局又是
Okay, if this ends in another case
你差点吃了你的动物朋友 我听够了
of you almost eating one of your animal friends, I can't.
好了 我要这么做
But... okay. This is... this is what I'm gonna do.
如果我们能让阿什利赞同我们
If we get Ashley on board,
剩下一切都能迎刃而解了
everything else will just fall into place.
我能说服陪审团认为有罪的人无罪
I convince juries that guilty people are innocent.
我肯定也可以说服阿什利
I can certainly convince Ashley
我们的派对创意酷毙了
that our party ideas are dope.
好 但别用酷毙了
Yeah, but don't say dope.
我不会说"酷毙"这个词的
I won't say dope.
你好 阿什
Hey, Ash.
听着
So, listen.
天啊 说得对
Oh, gosh. Oh, good call.
我想让这个派对再提升一个档次
Um, I'm thinking about kicking this party up a notch,
做点成熟的游...
more grown-up activi...
它还是...
Uh, I-I-it's still...
是的 天啊
Yeah. Yes, it is. My word.
找不到合适的号的时候
Kind of a tweener on sizes.
我们总是喜欢买小一号 对吧
And we always tend to go smaller, don't we?
人性如此 是不是
I mean, human nature, am I right?
总之 很多高中女生
Anyway, um, a lot of high-school girls
非常喜欢看图猜词
are really just falling in love with Pictionary,
我也有点... 天啊
and I sort of... um, uh... Oh, gosh.
小卡给我买的衣服 我...
Cam bought me this shirt, and I...
不敢相信我居然想怪小卡
can't believe I just tried to blame Cam.
米奇尔 要有责任感 自己的错自己担
Mitchell, take responsibility -- You eat bread, you billow.
总之 你的上衣真好看 我...
Anyway... your shirt is really nice, and I...
好吧 接电话吧
Yeah. Take the call.
没谁
Nobody.
再见 阿什
Bye, Ash.
性感帅哥
Hey, sexy!
这是要做什么
What's all this?
就是给你和我准备点特别的东西
Oh, just a little something special for you and I.
我要是你我就放下它们
I would put those away.
你要是乱碰乔的积木 他会疯的
Joe goes crazy if you play with his blocks.
或许该我们俩疯一疯了
Maybe it's time for us to get a little crazy.
过来
Come here.
我很怕这个
I was afraid of this.
这就是为什么我想和海莉慢慢来
This is why I was trying to slow things down with Haley.
女人们总是被我的身材吸引
Women are always drawn to me physically
非常强烈地吸引
in a very intense way.
结果经常在我们
Which often fizzles out
有感情交流前 热情就消失殆尽了
before we have a chance to connect emotionally.
所以...
So...
怎么了
Yes?
你的很多事情
There are so many things about you
我都不了解
that I just don't know.
我感觉《海莉》这本书仿佛才读了第一章
I feel, in the Book of Haley, I'm only in chapter one.
该翻篇了 多给我讲讲吧
Turn the page for me, girl.
什么
What?
要是我给你梳头 会不会帮你敞开心扉
Would it help you to open up if I were to brush your hair?
你是说性感的对话吗
You mean in a hot way?
我给我们准备了酒
I got us some wine.
你知道什么更好吗
You know what would be better?
两杯舒缓的绿茶
Two cups of soothing green tea
能充分调动我们的情感
to warm our emotional availability.
我们肯定谈得特别开心 我马上回来
Ooh, the places we will go. I'll be right back.
我希望这话听起来别太自负
I hope this doesn't sound conceited,
但大家都想要我
but everyone wants me.
我就知道安迪拒绝我
I just knew there had to be a rational reason
肯定有原因
Andy was rejecting me.
贝丝的海岸警卫队制服
Beth's Coast Guard uniform.
我不敢相信他还没忘了她
I can't believe he's not over her.
她穿六号的衣服
She's a size six!
谁动了我的积木
Who moved my blocks?!
好 Vi等于每秒367米
Okay, so, Vi equals 367 meters per second,
D等于0.00214 所以...
and D equals .00214, so th...
艾丽克斯 你知道我被闪电劈过吗
Alex, did you know I was struck by lightning?
不 不 不 现在没时间
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Not right now.
梅茜 继续
Maisie, continue.
我思路断了
Uh...I lost it.
那现在我们能谈谈我的事了吗
So...can we talk about my thing now?
好吧 听着 你非常帅
Okay, look, you're really hot,
在合适的时机
and under the right circumstances,
我会跟你亲热的 但是...
I could see myself making out with you, but...
但我们在努力复原
But we're trying to re-create
早上在电脑上做的功课 所以...
all the work that we lost on the computer this morning, so...
而且 每次你开口说话
Also, every time you open your mouth,
整个房间里都一股蠢味
you let out a cloud of stupid over the entire room.
反正我也不想和你们这种不合群的混在一起
I don't want to be in here with you losers anyway.
还有一件事...
And another thing...
我们能回到梅茜刚才说的话题吗
can we circle back to what Maisie just said?
出去
Get out!
-这么快就回来了 -根本没走
- Hey. Back already? - Never left.
泳池里的水还差一厘米
And now the pool's a centimeter
就要漫出来流进屋里了
from overflowing right in the house.
我得去把水抽出来
I got to pump the pool.
等等 等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
杰 我希望你去酒吧
Jay, I want you in that bar,
我需要感觉自己还是个男人
and I need to feel like a man.
我去把泳池的水抽出来
Let me pump your pool.
好吧 一个水管在泳池里 另一个...
All right. One hose in the pool, the other one...
杰 这话还要对我说吗
Jay, shh. It's me.
对 我还是自己来吧
You're right. I'll do it.
不 不 不 我能行 我能行
No, no, no, no, no. I got it. I got it.
歌洛莉亚 我两个小时就回来
Gloria, I'll be back in a couple hours!
什么 混蛋 谁没关门
What the... Son of a bitch! Who left the door open?!
斯黛拉 斯黛拉
Stella! Stella!
它很可能跑出去了
She probably got outside.
到底是谁没关门
Who the hell left the door open?!
不是我
Not me!
Nope.
天啊
Oh, God.
我做了什么
What have I done?
斯黛拉 斯黛拉
Stella! Stella?
都弄好了 杰 弄得特别棒
All set, here, Jay! Working like a charm!
承认吧
Admit it!
你没想到我真的能...
You didn't think I could actually...
不 不 你要做什么
Oh, no, no, no. What are you doing?
你要做什么
What are you doing?
这衣服就放在菲尔的后备箱里
Wha-- well, Phil had this in his trunk
我也不相信你跟阿什利能谈成功
and I didn't have faith in your "Talk to Ashley" plan, so...
所以你就决定要扮血色小丑吗
So you decided to go with Bleeding Clown?
那你和阿什利谈得怎么样啊
Well, how did your talk with Ashley go?
你是把衣服钉上了吗
Is your shirt stapled?
别管这事
Yea... Don't worry about it.
我绝不要让我们的女儿接下来一年
Okay, I will not have our daughter eat lunch
都跟公鸡一起吃饭的
with a rooster for the next year.
这里就有一个专业的小丑
We have a fully-licensed clown right here.
我敢说
And I defy
不会有任何孩子不喜欢小丑的
any child to not be delighted by that!
小丑什么的
A clown.
你不喜欢小丑吗
You don't like clowns?
拜托
Please.
真是够了
You know what?
闭嘴吧 阿什利
Shut up, Ashley!
杰 杰
Jay! Jay.
泳池的水流到屋里了
The water is coming inside the house from the pool!
当然了
Of course it is.
因为是菲尔负责去抽水
Because Phil was supposed to pump it out!
其实 有一个应急阀
Actually, there's an emergency valve.
在泳池最北边 我知道那个应急阀
At the north end of the pool. I know that valve.
我会打开应急阀的
I'm gonna open that valve.
你做得还不够多吗
Haven't you done enough already?
拜托 我需要这么做
Please! I need this!
再说了 现在还有谁敢
And who else would dare to jump
跳进那池子里呢
in that pool right now anyway?
我
Me!
我不知道你们怎么想
I'm not sure about the rest of you,
但我要在雨中穿着衣服游泳
but I'm going swimming, in the rain, in my clothes!
泳池派对
Pool party!
我不会...
I am not gonna...
我可以去吗
Can I come?
随你便咯 阿什利
Do whatever you want, Ashley.
没错
Yeah.
她跟来了吗 别回头
Is she following? Don't look back.
所有人退后
Everybody stand back!
我打开了阀门
I opened the valve!
真为她高兴
I'm happy for her.
你老公正在外面半裸着
Your husband's outside half naked.
你还有时间下楼
There's still time to go downstairs
羞辱他的身材
and body shame him if you like.
好吧 让我们来解决这件事
Okay. Let's you and me get this over with.
好吧 你让我有点开始疑惑了
Okay, you're really putting on mixed signals here.
别说话了 好吗
Please stop talking. Okay.
你当然对自己的身体有不安全感
Of course you're insecure about your body.
你还是个青少年
You're a teenager.
这是每个青少年都会有的
It's part of the job description.
如果真要去什么裸泳的话
But if this whole skinny-dipping thing ever even happens,
你完全不用担心
you have nothing to worry about.
-对你来说当然简单... -你还在说话
- Easy for you to... - You're still talking.
你完全不用担心
You have nothing to worry about
因为没人会看你
because nobody's going to be looking at you,
因为其他的孩子
because all those other kids
都会忙着担心自己的身材
are gonna be too preoccupied with their own insecurities.
那如果他们看了呢
But if they do?
你会没事的
You'll be fine.
你是我见过最自信的小孩
You're the most confident kid I have ever met,
这永远都是性感的
and that is always sexy.
谢谢 克莱尔
Thanks, Claire.
不知道这句话对你有没有帮助
And if this helps you in any way,
我也一直觉得你很性感
I've always found you sexy, too.
太好了
Super.
别不开心了
Stop pouting!
这太不像你了
That's so not you.
谁在乎你穿着小丑的服装
Who cares that you dressed up as a clown,
在很多面镜子前吓到自己呢
then scared yourself in many mirrors?
其实更让我难堪的是
Actually, what's even more embarrassing
我以为如果我能冲进那屋子里
is that I thought if I ran into that fun house
抓住那小孩
and grabbed that kid,
所有人就会觉得
everyone would look at me
我是那个我一直都想当的英雄
like the hero I always wanted to be.
纠正一下 让我最难堪的是
Correction. What's most embarrassing
从那时开始我做的所有事
is everything I've done since then
都是为了弥补第一件事
to try to make up for the first thing.
你在说什么英雄
What are you talking about? "Hero"?
你绝不仅是个英雄
You're so much more than that.
你有缺点
You have flaws.
你经常摔倒
You fall down a lot.
你吓到自己
You frighten yourself.
你甚至开不了一罐果酱 你总是哭
You cannot even open a jar. You cry all the time.
我准备好听你接下来的安慰了
I'm really ready for this to build into a compliment.
重点是你能自得其乐
The point is that you are comfortable with yourself,
让你身边的人都感到舒适
and you make people around you feel comfortable.
他们觉得能够跟你谈心
They feel that they can talk to you.
那是你的超能力
That's your superpower!
池子放干了 裂缝补好了 发电机工作了
Pool's drained, leaks are fixed, generator's running,
我要去见我朋友了
and I'm meeting my buddies.
为什么呢 杰 为什么你一定要出去呢
Why, Jay? Why you have to go out?
外面可是在刮飓风
It's a hurricane outside!
我就是要出去
I just do.
我觉得你可能刚刚拧松了...
I think you probably loosened it with the...
别说了
Don't.
这是你珍贵的制服
Here's your precious uniform!
那是贝丝的
That's Beth's.
你终于承认你还爱着她了
Oh, so you admit you're still in love with her!
什么
What?
只是冷漠地打个招呼是会让人受伤的
Just saying "Hey" hurts, doesn't it?
海莉
Haley!
站住 你在干什么
Stop! What are you doing?
你不想吻我 你甚至不想碰我
You won't kiss me. You won't even touch me.
然后我又找到了贝丝的制服
And then I find Beth's uniform?
你告诉我吧
So you tell me, okay?
你到底想用它来干嘛
What do you do with it anyway?
你 你 你闻着它 抱着它
You -- you -- you sniff it, you snuggle it,
你把它挂在衣架上 然后和它跳舞吗
you put it on a coat rack and dance with it?!
我要把贝丝的东西还给她
I'm sending Beth's things back to her,
我把制服熨好只是因为我爱我的国家
and I got her uniform pressed because I love my country.
所以说 你和贝丝 你们...
So, y-you and Beth, you...
没有什么贝丝 只有你
There is no Beth. There's only you.
我只是想放慢我们的进度
I'm just trying to slow us down a little.
我们的关系几乎是从一半开始的
We kind of started this whole thing off in the middle.
我只是想在感情上
I just want us to catch up emotionally
跟上肉体的进度 这样热情才不会燃烧殆尽
to where we are physically so we don't burn out.
我们不会燃烧殆尽的
We're not going to burn out.
在我们勾搭上之前我就喜欢你了
I liked you way before we ever hooked up.
我只是想让我们的关系跟我们偷爱时一样好
I just want our relationship to be as good as our affair.
我们甚至连一次浪漫的约会都没有过
I mean, we never even had a romantic first date.
我知道
I know.
也许我们该等到一个完美时刻
Maybe we should wait for the perfect moment
恰当地开展我们的关系
so we can start our relationship right.
既特别又神奇的事 像电影里一样
Something special and magical, like in the movies.
你想让我干什么
What do you want me to do,
穿过一个飞机追你吗
chase you through an airport?
我觉得现在已经够浪漫了
I think we got it.
没错
Oh, yeah.
不是吧
Come on!
一棵该死的树堵住了街道
A damn tree's blocking the street.
我需要电锯
I need my chainsaw.
杰 我知道你没问我的意见...
Jay, I know you didn't ask my advice...
很高兴你意识到了 我一整天都被困在这了
I'm glad you noticed that. I've been stuck here all day.
现在我要去酒吧了
Now, I'm going to that bar!
我现在最不需要的就是再耽搁
The last thing I need's another delay.
该死的电锯究竟在哪里
Where the hell's the chainsaw?!
就在那里
It's right there.
我去不了了 是吧
I'm not gonna get there, am I?
我们不必聊这个
We don't have to talk about it.
我以前海军的战友大杰克今天去世了
Old Navy buddy of mine, Big Jake, died today.
我们部队有个传统
Guys in my unit have a tradition
我们其中有谁去世了 其他人
whereas, when one of us goes, the rest of us,
无论身在何处 都要找到最近的爱尔兰酒吧
no matter where we are, find the nearest Irish pub,
在七点 举杯默哀
at 7 o'clock, silently toast the fallen.
开始有十个人
Started with 10 guys.
只剩我们四个了
Four of us left.
也许早该跟歌洛莉亚说的
Probably should have told Gloria about it,
但我不知道
but I don't know.
我们一起经历了一些挫折
We all went through some rough stuff together...
很难提起
Hard to talk about.
谢谢
Thanks.
菲尔
Phil.
我们为什么就是记不起最后这里呢
Why can't we remember this last piece?
今天早上才想到的
We just had it this morning.
两位 我知道你们很忙
Hey, guys. I know you're busy,
但你们觉不觉得人被电击后
but do you think being hit by lightning
会变聪明呢
can make people smarter?
滚出去
Get out of here.
是啊 可能是个未解之谜吧
Yeah. It's probably just a myth.
现在网上满是些疯狂的事
There's so much crazy stuff written on the Internet these days.
原来 她们第一次想出来的时候
Turns out, when they figured it out the first time,
那个公式就在我一张自拍的背景上
the formula was in the background of a selfie I took.
总之 如果你们不觉得电击能使人聪明
Anyway, if you don't think lightning can do that,
那就肯定不能
it must not be true.
毕竟 你们是我认识的最聪明的人
After all, you are the smartest people I know.